MAR JOHN CORNELIO

WEB DEVELOPER

0916-826-9678

mc.marjohncornelio@gmail.com

O Dreamland Ville, Brgy. Kaypian, San Jose Del Monte, Bulacan



PROFILE

Graduate of Bachelor of Science in Information Technology at Bulacan State University - Sarmiento Campus. Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, with a passion for using the latest front-end libraries and frameworks to create engaging user experiences

WORKSHOPS / SEMINARS

Advance Front-End Web Development

Bayan Academy - JPMC IndemandPh May 2022 - June 2022

Back-End Web Development 101

Bayan Academy - JPMC IndemandPh August 2022 - September 2022

SKILLS

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Familiar in JavaScript framework such as React.is.
- Skilled in implementing front-end libraries and frameworks like Bootstrap and Material UI.
- Basic understanding with a variety of programming languages including Java, Python, and C
- Familiar in server-side language and database management like Node.js and MySQL
- Experienced in version control and collaboration using Git and GitHub
- Technical knowledge of computer hardware, software, and networking
- Experience in maintaining and monitoring computer systems and networks to ensure optimal performance and security
- Ability to provide technical support and troubleshoot issues for end-users.

EDUCATION

BS Information Technology

Bulacan State Unitversity - Sarmiento 2019 - 2023

TVL Track - Computer Programming

San Jose Del Monte National High School 2017 - 2019

WORK EXPERIENCES

Freelance Autocad Operator

2022 - present

Create 2D and 3D models of architectural, or electrical designs to be used in construction processes.

IT Associate - Internship

Jan 2023 - April 2023 Qualimed Hospital Altaraza Spine Road, Barangay Tungkong Mangga, 3023, San Jose del Monte

Assist in the management of an IT infrastructure of an organization as well as providing technical support for computer systems and troubleshooting issues encountered by end users

CHARACTER REFERENCES

Christian D. Quiring

IT Head Manager Qualimed Hospital - CSJDM, Bulacan 0916-329-5222

Aldrin John Tamayo

Software Engineer Oracle Corporation Philippines - Makati 0906-363-4097